all right so I just found a new
broadcast to me anyway they're on like
episode 1718 which I'm gonna catch up
with in the next two weeks because I'm
going to listen to an episode a day and
critique it's the wrong word just offer
my opinion on what it sparked in me or
my what I see what they're talking about
related to the global cooperative that I
have in visions and so the guy who does
it is named Michael Elbert and it is
revolutions II and this episode one is
called why vision why strategy and so a
lot of what he talks about is that we
need a vision and strategy something we
can work together towards instead of and
what I thought what it sparked was we
have the same things we desire but we
have different things we fear and so we
critique and argue about what we're
scared about we're more scared about our
family we're more scared about our own
individual health or and those things
play off each other right we can't
what's the biggest priority isn't racism
is it homophobia is it is it my kids
being fed versus what we desire is often
not unique to us right we do desire kids
to be fed we desire to be healthy we
desire to be have abundance in our own
lives and so that was was interesting
and it like what I know I struggle with
presenting what it is I envision in a
positive what we get what we get vision
as opposed to why we need it because
we're about to have a terrifying future
and I live in both of those worlds I
live in the okay this is going to be a
shitstorm in my kids lifetime if we
don't do something about it and also
with what I'm able to see as possible in
the future
a future I am actively working towards I
do have vision and I have strategy I
just really wish I could
educate it in a way that it works and I
know that part of what we need to do and
what I've struggled with because I'm
well doing the work I'm doing I've come
across many movements that are amazing
and had conversations with people like
Nicole from the trance the transition I
think that I'm part of but there is this
weird like we don't join together and
part of it is somebody creates their own
visioning values and then you're either
going to come on board and work from
that point or you're not and I long
before searching other people to work on
to join the project I want to create new
ok well what are the things that would
need to be in place if I found an
organization or a group that held these
values I would jump on board and help
them to the best of my ability and for
me it's things like democracy or
something equivalent that people get a
voice that it's transparent that it's
not well we created this and now you can
either be part of the inner circle or
not part of the inner circle I want
anyone who comes on board to be able to
be as instrumental as they desire I want
it to be voluntary I want it to be
something that inspires me to be my best
self to I need it to not be able as' and
a lot of them are really able is and
we're gonna get to the later podcast
later which I'm sure I will have
comments on and everyone's ablest I mean
unless you have every single disability
that is possible on this planet you're
going to have some internal ableism
about your stuff and other other peoples
that having more intelligence makes you
more worthy and whatever that
intelligence is then having more
physical ability makes you more worthy
and I don't think anything makes you
want worthy I think each of us is a
unique entity that is worthy of being on
this planet having our needs met and
getting to contribute in our own unique
way and it's about organizing that
effort in a way that collectively moves
us forward so for the individual it's
easy and fun and for the group there's
powerful momentum forward and I can see
how we get there with a technology
cooperative
that we all own together and anyone can
come on board and be a part of and I see
like the first communication platform
that facilitates that facilitates
although the communication platform
might not be able to be done in a
transparent open way because we don't
yet have the tools once we have the
social media platform that we own that
we can help Co evolve as we can say
what's not working on what is working
it's designed for a meaningful
conversation then all of the meaningful
conversations can take place and we can
tackle all of the problems by passing
the current government and for-profit
corporations and just creating solutions
together once we have the tools to be
able to do that which starts with just a
conversation so I don't know how much
I've talked about that episode but I am
excited to have found this podcast I
said it was revolutions II episode 1 why
vision why strategy and the person who
does it is Michael Albert if I can bring
my own writing here a given and what I
got from this first episode is for the
vision I need to give to the world I
need to present it often more often in
the pro side in how do we refill the cup
instead of arguing about how it got
empty in the first place
and that it's empty and convincing
people it's empty how do we fill up a
cup and that is what I am here to this
planet to do is to create a world that
works for everyone including allowing
everyone to contribute to that world and
the creation of it in their own unique
way so and I'm also posting daily now so
this is today's video my response to
revolutions II which I might be doing
daily unless something else sparks take
care please like and subscribe
as my kid says at the end of all of our
videos that are yet to be online